



Eliecer Sánchez Mora

Date of birth: 05/08/1995 | **Nationality:** Venezuelan | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:**

(+356) 79548102 (Mobile) | Email address: eliecer.sanchez47@gmail.com | Website:

https://eliecersm-portfolio.netlify.app | LinkedIn:

www.linkedin.com/in/eliecer-smora-22688a26a | WhatsApp Messenger: +356 7954 8102 |

Address: Flat, Venezuela (Home)

ABOUT ME

Goal-oriented individual with a pleasant personality and a tenacity that knows no restrictions. I can be a multitasking person, willing to meet the goal of the company and work as a team.

As a Frontend developer, I really like working with JavaScript (libraries, frameworks) and I keep up learning everyday. Based on my past experience and expertise into the programming world, I manage good logic and I know how to work under pressure, I am creative with a positive mentality to solve problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

02/10/2023 - 04/03/2024 San Gwan, Malta

REACT / NEXTJS FRONTEND DEVELOPER KANON GAMING LIMITED

- Develop new pages and features for Casino's websites in Sweden and Denmark using JavaScript, React.js and Next.js. CSS for styles and Firebase.
- Work on Backoffice company for provider's games releases
- Code Improving, Testing, Refactoring, Bugs Fixes, Clean code, Git Actions

10/06/2024 - 05/11/2024 Aragua, Venezuela

REACT NATIVE AND JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER (FREELANCE) LIMONBYTE AND HIDROAGUA C.A

- Development of React Native App using Expo Router
- Code Improving, Refactoring, Bugs Fixes, Clean code, GitHub
- Frontend web tasks with JavaScript also using React and Tailwind CSS

02/08/2022 - 02/02/2023 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

WEB DESIGNER FREELANCER EL TUNAL

- Development with JavaScript's library React and developing UI
- Support API, services and more with JavaScript runtime environment NodeJS

02/01/2022 - 01/12/2022 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

JAVASCRIPT SELF-TAUGHT

- Development with JavaScript, building projects.
- Improving HTML5 Skills
- Improving CSS skills and Tailwind CSS

30/04/2019 - 31/08/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

IAVA SE DEVELOPER LARA STATE GOBERMENT

- Improve worker assintance system built in Java SE

01/01/2018 - 30/12/2018 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

JAVA SE DEVELOPER UNIVERSITY INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY "ANTONIO JOSÉ DE SUCRE" AND THEN FREELANCER

- I have developed an Automated system for managing graduates of my university
- As freelancer I developed an Automated inventory system for a client

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/09/2014 - 01/02/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

UNIVERSITY TECHNICIAN IN COMPUTER SCIENCE University Institute of Technology "Antonio José de Sucre"

Website http://www.utsbarguisimeto.edu.ve/

21/08/2016 - 26/10/2016 Baquisimeto, Venezuela

PROGRAMMING LOGIC AND JAVA SE LEVEL 1 COURSE CADIF1

Website https://cadif1.com/

22/11/2017 - 22/03/2019 Barquisimeto, Venezuela

ENGLISH CONVERSATION 1 COURSE Westminster

Website https://gelvez.com.ve/barquisimeto/idiomas/27625-idiomas-westminster.html

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **SPANISH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Reactjs | VisalStudio Code | CSS | React, Next.js, React Native | Version Control System (Git) | CSS Modules | Tailwind CSS | Git | Postman API | Mongo DB and PostgreSQL | Bootstrap | Nodejs | Socket.io | Express js | Google Firebase, Oracle Cloud Infrastructure | Atlassian stack (Jira, Confluence, ...) | Git, Slack Communication | Version Control Systems: Github | Adatbázis-kezelés (MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Access) | NVM

APTITUDES

Good communication, empathic and work really well within a team

Analytical skills and work well under pressure

Ability to solve problems

Willingness to learn and grow

Having a good business sense

Ability to handle criticism

Assistance arrange

REFERENCES

Mr Luc Young - Lead team Software Developer at Kanon Gaming Limited

Email: luc-young@outlook.com

Tlf: +356 7700 9254